# KILLORAN LEHENBAUER

Gilbert, AZ 85233 • (602) 677-6512 • <u>k.lehenbauer13@gmail.com</u> LinkedIn: <u>https://www.linkedin.com/in/killoran-lehenbauer</u> Portfolio: <u>https://toxicnerd13.github.io/Updated-Portfolio/</u> Github: https://github.com/ToxicNerd13

#### **SUMMARY**

Full stack developer with a love of organization and editing. Possesses a curious mind with a penchant for researching and solving puzzles. Personable, focused personality that thrives in a fast-paced work environment. Known among coworkers to be an excellent communicator and team player.

#### **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

Languages: HTML5, CSS3, Bootstrap, Javascript, jQuery, Node.js, Express, MySQL, MongoDB,

React.js

Applications: Visual Studio Code, MySQL Workbench, Git Bash, Robo 3T

#### **PROJECTS**

# **Excer-Tracker (Full Stack)**

https://github.com/ToxicNerd13/exercise-tracker | https://excertracker-kill.herokuapp.com/

- A web app designed to help users log and track their exercise habits.
- Designed and created cloud database to store usernames and exercise logs, utilized REST API to allow users to create/edit/delete exercises, used React to streamline the app into reusable components
- HTML5, CSS3, Bootstrap, Javascript, REST API, JSON, Node.js, Express, React.js, jQuery, MongoDB, Mongoose

#### Game On (Full Stack)

https://github.com/hannahm63/project-2 | https://game-on3.herokuapp.com

- A site where gamers can search game titles and see available platforms & reviews. They can also leave comments on games they've played.
- Created and maintained database to store user comments, communicated with 3<sup>rd</sup> party API to display game info and comments on page
- HTML5, CSS3, Bootstrap, Javascript, REST API, JSON, Node.js, Express, Handlebars, jQuery, MySQL, Sequelize

## **Memory Game (Front-end)**

https://github.com/ToxicNerd13/Memory-Game | https://toxicnerd13.github.io/Memory-Game/

 A browser game that challenges the player to only click on each rearranging picture once.

- Used React to dynamically display photos and rearrange them when clicked, kept track
  of score and win/loss conditions
- HTML5, CSS3, Bootstrap, Javascript, React.js, Node.js, JSON

## **EXPERIENCE**

### **Clockwork Pizza**

Delivery Driver • Tempe, AZ • 08/2019 - 08/2020

 Navigate to addresses in an efficient and timely manner, answer phones and accurately input orders into POS system, up-sell customers on drinks & desserts (increasing sales by 15% on average).

## **Luxe Lounge**

Lead Server/Bartender • Maricopa, AZ • 08/2018 – 07/2019

- Recognized and fulfilled customer needs, coordinated with other servers as a team, maintained evolving knowledge of craft cocktails and food specials, navigated a glitchy POS system and improvised workarounds as needed
- Awarded Employee of the Month for March 2019, recognized for attention to detail and glowing customer feedback. Promoted to trainer within 3 months after showing confidence and skill in customer care.

#### **EDUCATION**

## University of Arizona Coding Bootcamp - Gilbert, AZ

Full Stack Web Development Certificate, 02/2020

A 24-week intensive program focused on gaining technical programming skills in HTML5, CSS3, Javascript, jQuery, Bootstrap, Firebase, Node.js, MySQL, MongoDB, Express, Handlebars.js & React.js

## Mesa Community College - Mesa, AZ

Associate of Arts Degree, 06/2017